Guide to the Syria Collection of photographs AD.MC.036
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Wedding Portrait Series (Box 6)
  - A studio portrait of a couple in their wedding outfits., 1963; ref1278; Triage Photo Dadour, Aleppo, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.5 x 17.5 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Weddings; Head Covers/Veils; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Men; Women; English Writing
  - A studio portrait of a couple in their wedding outfits., Circa 1960-1970; ref1279; Photo Kevork, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.5 x 13.8 cm (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Weddings; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Men; Women; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Head Covers/Veils
  - A studio portrait of a couple in their wedding outfits., Circa 1960-1970; ref1280; Photo Kevork, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.5 x 13.8 cm (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Men; Women; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Head Covers/Veils; Weddings
  - A studio portrait of a couple in their wedding outfits., Circa 1960-1970; ref1281; Photo Kevork, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.5 x 13.8 cm (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Men; Women; Weddings; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Syria